{
  "frames": [
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 256,
          "y": 64
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 0.20000000298023224,
          "y": 0.05000000074505806
        },
        "displayName": "cloud_0",
        "filenameStem": "cloud_0",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 0,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 128,
          "width": 512
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 0.10000000149011612,
          "width": 0.40000000596046448
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 1024,
        "left": 1024
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.625244140625,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.531494140625,
        "bottom": 0.500244140625,
        "left": 0.500244140625,
        "right": 0.749755859375,
        "top": 0.562255859375
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0625,
        "width": 0.25
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 256,
          "y": 128
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 0.20000000298023224,
          "y": 0.10000000149011612
        },
        "displayName": "cloud_1",
        "filenameStem": "cloud_1",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 1,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 256,
          "width": 512
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 0.20000000298023224,
          "width": 0.40000000596046448
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 768,
        "left": 0
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.125244140625,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.437744140625,
        "bottom": 0.375244140625,
        "left": 0.000244140625,
        "right": 0.249755859375,
        "top": 0.499755859375
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.125,
        "width": 0.25
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 512,
          "y": 256
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 0.40000000596046448,
          "y": 0.20000000298023224
        },
        "displayName": "cloud_2",
        "filenameStem": "cloud_2",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 2,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 512,
          "width": 1024
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 0.40000000596046448,
          "width": 0.80000001192092896
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 0,
        "left": 0
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.250244140625,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.125244140625,
        "bottom": 0.000244140625,
        "left": 0.000244140625,
        "right": 0.499755859375,
        "top": 0.249755859375
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.25,
        "width": 0.5
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 512,
          "y": 128
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 0.40000000596046448,
          "y": 0.10000000149011612
        },
        "displayName": "cloud_3",
        "filenameStem": "cloud_3",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 3,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 256,
          "width": 1024
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 0.20000000298023224,
          "width": 0.80000001192092896
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 0
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.250244140625,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.312744140625,
        "bottom": 0.250244140625,
        "left": 0.000244140625,
        "right": 0.499755859375,
        "top": 0.374755859375
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.125,
        "width": 0.5
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 256,
          "y": 128
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 0.20000000298023224,
          "y": 0.10000000149011612
        },
        "displayName": "cloud_4",
        "filenameStem": "cloud_4",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 4,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 256,
          "width": 512
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 0.20000000298023224,
          "width": 0.40000000596046448
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 768,
        "left": 512
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.375244140625,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.437744140625,
        "bottom": 0.375244140625,
        "left": 0.250244140625,
        "right": 0.499755859375,
        "top": 0.499755859375
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.125,
        "width": 0.25
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 128,
          "y": 64
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 0.10000000149011612,
          "y": 0.05000000074505806
        },
        "displayName": "cloud_5",
        "filenameStem": "cloud_5",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 5,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 128,
          "width": 256
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 0.10000000149011612,
          "width": 0.20000000298023224
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 1024,
        "left": 1536
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.812744140625,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.531494140625,
        "bottom": 0.500244140625,
        "left": 0.750244140625,
        "right": 0.874755859375,
        "top": 0.562255859375
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0625,
        "width": 0.125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 256,
          "y": 128
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 0.20000000298023224,
          "y": 0.10000000149011612
        },
        "displayName": "cloud_6",
        "filenameStem": "cloud_6",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 6,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 256,
          "width": 512
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 0.20000000298023224,
          "width": 0.40000000596046448
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 768,
        "left": 1024
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.625244140625,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.437744140625,
        "bottom": 0.375244140625,
        "left": 0.500244140625,
        "right": 0.749755859375,
        "top": 0.499755859375
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.125,
        "width": 0.25
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 256,
          "y": 128
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 0.20000000298023224,
          "y": 0.10000000149011612
        },
        "displayName": "cloud_7",
        "filenameStem": "cloud_7",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 7,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 256,
          "width": 512
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 0.20000000298023224,
          "width": 0.40000000596046448
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 768,
        "left": 1536
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.875244140625,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.437744140625,
        "bottom": 0.375244140625,
        "left": 0.750244140625,
        "right": 0.999755859375,
        "top": 0.499755859375
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.125,
        "width": 0.25
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 256,
          "y": 128
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 0.20000000298023224,
          "y": 0.10000000149011612
        },
        "displayName": "cloud_8",
        "filenameStem": "cloud_8",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 8,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 256,
          "width": 512
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 0.20000000298023224,
          "width": 0.40000000596046448
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 1024,
        "left": 0
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.125244140625,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.562744140625,
        "bottom": 0.500244140625,
        "left": 0.000244140625,
        "right": 0.249755859375,
        "top": 0.624755859375
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.125,
        "width": 0.25
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 256,
          "y": 128
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 0.20000000298023224,
          "y": 0.10000000149011612
        },
        "displayName": "cloud_9",
        "filenameStem": "cloud_9",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 9,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 256,
          "width": 512
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 0.20000000298023224,
          "width": 0.40000000596046448
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 1024,
        "left": 512
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.375244140625,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.562744140625,
        "bottom": 0.500244140625,
        "left": 0.250244140625,
        "right": 0.499755859375,
        "top": 0.624755859375
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.125,
        "width": 0.25
      }
    }
  ],
  "options": 0,
  "size": {
    "height": 2048,
    "width": 2048
  }
}
